English-language manuscript verse in the Houghton Library, circa 1000-1820: First-line index.
English-language manuscript verse in the Houghton Library circa 1000-1820,
Scenes that soothed Or charmed me young, no longer young, I find (incomplete) MS Am 1136 (64), 1
Scented first by heav'nly breath MS Eng 612, ii, 118
Scholars should know, all fire in motion lies (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 99v
Scotland is my native land MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 254v
Scotland, thy weather like a modish wife MS Keats 3.13, i, 62v
Scots out of Berwick and of Aberdeen MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 276v
Scots wha' hae wi' Wallace bled MS Eng 877, 1
Screams round the Arch-druid's brow the seamewwhite MS Eng 327(2)
Search then the ruling passion, there alone (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 40v
Season of mists and mellow fruitfulness MS Keats 3.2, 142; MS Keats 3.6, p. 34; MS Keats 1.64, 1v; MS Keats 2.27
Seditious actions to destruction tend MS Eng 614, 98
See, as they creep along the river side (incomplete) MS Keats 2.17.2
See as they crept along the river side (incomplete) MS Keats 2.17.4
See, Chloe, how the new blown rose MS Eng 895, 71v
See, Corydon, the flocks give way MS Eng 629, 39
See! from the clouds the spring descends in show'rs (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 110
See, from the golden tinted east MS Mus 237, ii, 3
See here the stork provides with tender care MS Typ 14, 25
See here thy ransomed servant, see MS Eng 614, 119
See here Ulysses' men transformed strange to hear MS Typ 14, 86v
See how beneath the moonbeam's smile MS Eng 630, 2v
See how Phoebus welketh in the west (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 135v
See! how the fields are gay around (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 114
See how the poor soul trembles, Like a weak callow bird, torn from its nest (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 55v
See how the willing earth gave way MS Eng 629, 32v
See how thy captive lark MS Eng 612, ii, 76
See India's triad wield their blood-stained rods (incomplete) MS Am 1448 (nos. 20-63), 52
See much, pay lytell, and lerne to soffar in tyme MS Eng 1482, Addit 29729, 130
See my past life is now no more MS Eng 636F, 126
See Newton's prism, to the sight MS Eng 569.68, 3
See! night has thinned her shades. The watchful bird MS Eng 611, i, 23
See Phoebus now, as once for Phaeton (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 102v
See, Selborne spreads her boldest beauties round MS Eng 731, folder 165
See, sir, how as the sun's hot masculine flame MS Eng 966.5, 122v
See, sirs, see here! a doctor rare, who travails much at home MS Eng 1038.1, 28
See, Stella, yonder picture see MS Eng 612, ii, 88v
See, Sylvia, see the sparkling lamp of day MS Eng 612, ii, 30v
See that your love may never alter MS Eng 686, 13
See! the boy storms the bird's weak citadel MS Eng 612, ii, 115
See the bright taper useless burns MS Eng 624, 62
See the kind shepherd, Jesus, stands *82-408, 13
See the lovely morning rise MS Eng 612, ii, 31
See the rash boy from the steep mountain's brow *82-408, 113
See the squibs and hear the bells (incomplete) MS Eng 1503 (3), vol. ii, p. 128 tipped in
See this little mistress here MS Eng 247.5, 60
See! thro' th'encumber'd air the pond'rous bomb (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 108
See, to the sun the butterfly displays (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 43
See, to the west, he downward bends his way (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 42
See, too! responsive, with her holiest strains (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 25v
See where she is! how her affections move (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 27v
See where she lies, Arsanes! she, she's dead (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 32v
See where she lies; her eyes chained up in sleep (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 31
See where the farmer, with a master's eye MS Eng 611, i, 58
See! where yon' vine in soft embraces weaves (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 110v
See! winter comes with all its horrid train MS Eng 616, i, 57
See with what noble pride she steps? That state (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 30v
See yonder about the midst he lies MS Eng 686, 53v
Seeing the springing day from far (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 78v
Seek not for Paradise with curious eye MS Eng 611, i, 110v
Seek not thou to find The sacred counsels of almighty mind (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 60
Seek wisdom chiefly to attain MS Eng 1503 (3), i, 84
Seek you to know what keeps the mind MS Eng 555, 19v
Seek you to train your favorite boy MS Eng 1038.2, 15v
Sees not my love how time resumes MS Eng 631, 64
See'st thou those jewels that she wears MS Eng 626, 7v
Seest thou yonder craggy rock (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 74v
Seethe for the blinkin queen MS Eng 1504, 9
Seize wisdom, ere 'tis torment to be wise (incomplete) MS Eng 680, verso of final leaf
Seldom and short be all our happiest hours MS Eng 1285, 73
Seleucus, you know the soul of our design MS Thr 7, 3
Send back again my heart to me MS Eng 626, 8
Send back those long strayed eyes to me MS Eng 895, 86v
Send forth, dear Julian, all thy books MS Eng 633, 3v; MS Eng 585, 21v
Send him to Bedlam, Sirs! 'twill never do *44-981, 3v
Send home those long strayed eyes to me MS Eng 512, 50v
Send home my long strayed eyes to me MS Eng 966.1, 16; MS Eng 966.7, 1; MS Eng 966.5, 134; MS Eng 966.4, 213v
Send me some token that my hope may live MS Eng 966.7, 20v; MS Eng 966.5, 157
Send me some tokens that my love may live MS Eng 966.1, 34
Send o'er mankind your searching eye, and show (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 108
Senseless bravado, Thy peevish age grown testy in th' extreme (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 55v
Septitious rich, a miser most of all MS Typ 14, 13v
Serene the morn, now Zephyr's gentle breeze MS Eng 611, ii, 57v
Set on to the temple first where we may pay (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 17
Seven planets they do grace the skies (incomplete) MS Eng 834, folder 48; MS Eng 629, 17v
Seven sisters in yonder ha' (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxviii, 891
Seven years the king he stayed MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 88v
Seven years the trencher sat (incomplete) MS Eng 1471, vii, 49
Seventh chapter of Isai MS Eng 1503 (3), iii, 3
Severity spoils ten, for one it mends (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 55
Seynt Stevene was a clerk MS Am 2349, xxii, 137
Shadows of visionary bliss from out (incomplete) MS Eng 947.8, Critique of poems... Watts
Shakespeare, the sprightliest, greatest, gentlest, wisest MS Keats 2.15.1, 34
Shall a new tide of differences MS Eng 645, 33
Shall conquest thy victorious ensign paint MS Eng 606, 34v
Shall Dicey's messengers of fame MS Eng 834, folder 49
Shall friendship wane because the world goes less MS Eng 645, 29v
Shall I an hearer be always, and never write MS Eng 699, 3
Shall I go force an Elegy? Abuse MS Eng 966.3, 118v; MS Eng 966.7, 92
Shall I like an hermit dwell MS Eng 966.7, 16v
Shall I not be bold when honor calls MS Eng 1038.1, 6v
Shall I stand still and tamely see such Smithfield bargains made for me MS Eng 1038.1, 37
Shall I wasting in despair MS Eng 1107, folder 11; EC7. Ox250.702p (originally ML 15.2F), item 9
Shall mortal beauties at a glance MS Eng 614, 57v
Shall poverty destroy us? Is the mind MS Eng 159, 17v
Shall Prigg your verses for his own report MS Eng 228, 26v
Shall that which rises out of nought complain (incomplete) MS Eng 680, verso of final leaf
Shall we leave Exeter, and with her all MS Eng 645, 60
Shall wit alone Apollo's footstool grace MS Eng 569.65, 13v
Shall's treat what else, for there in may be found MS Eng 645, 15v
Shalt thou, who seeks with eagle pinion (incomplete) MS Eng 947.8, Critique of poems...Watts
Shame of my life, disturber of my tomb MS Eng 636F, 150
Sharp pricks preserve the rose on every part MS Typ 14, 88v
Sharp witted Will to occupy some land MS Eng 645, 81
She also recommended him to God (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 7
She and the sun alone unchang'd appear (incomplete) MS Eng 602F, 29v
She booted him, she spurred him (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 27 and p. 31
She called up her seven sons (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 31
She ceasedmeantime in silence by Dunois MS Eng 265.3, 102
She could shape and she could sew MS Eng 1470, in envelope fastened to back cover
She couldna wash, and she could na' wring (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, in envelope fastened to back cover
She danc'd along with vague regardless eyes (incomplete) MS Keats 2.21
She dreamt her womb brought forth a mighty flame (incomplete) MS Eng 631, 12v
She dwelt among the untrodden ways MS Eng 1094, 31; MS Eng 601.66, 25
She ended: and with lips of rosy hue (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 68v
She for a mistress fain would I enjoy MS Eng 686, 34
She for her honor oweth you obedience MS Eng 540
She gave him a gay gold ring (incomplete) MS Am 2349, v, p. 57; MS Am 2349, xxi, 120; MS Eng 1470, 7; MS Eng 862.1, loose leaf at end
She got three drops of boiling lead (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 27 and p. 32
She had a thousand jadish tricks MS Eng 1132, 5
She has cause for sorrow. The shock was sudden, and might well alarm (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 101
She has wit and good humor, excellent (incomplete) MS Eng 616, i, 18v
She in her own would merge the Eternal Will P.S. (incomplete) MS Eng 327, "To S. Wilkinson, Sept. 21"; MS Eng 327(73)
She is a sink of sin whose turning wit MS Eng 702, 15
She is a woman: and the ways unto her (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2 (twice)
She is not out, but holds up still one eye MS Eng 645, 20v
She kiss'd his mouth and she comb'd his hair (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 262
She knew her lady's master key (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 57v
She leant her back against a thorn MS Eng 1444, 10
She leant her back until a thorn (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxii, 133
She left us young, she died in early life MS Eng 1504, 20
She, like a moon in wane, Faded before him, cower'd, nor could restrain (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 50
She lives but I could wish her dead. Rash man. Why should your envy swell so high (incomplete) MS Eng 616, i, 1
She might as easily have sought (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 133v
She might have numbered out the stars in sin (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 7v
She never blamed him never MS Keats 3.13, ii, 34v
She noted all she ever read (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 94v
She o'er all hearts and toasts must reign MS Eng 768 (vol. 1), 34v
She plays and sings too, dances and discourses (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
She psalms would often sing in meter MS Eng 612, ii, 42v
She sailed West, she sailed East MS Eng 1470, 90; MS Eng 1470, 13v
She sent him a purse o' the red gowd (incomplete) MS Eng 1471, vi, 11v
She served them up, she served them down (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 31
She sighed when she bade me farewell MS Eng 692, 57v
She sinks. Idolatress of formal skill P.S. (incomplete) MS Eng 327, "To S. Wilkinson, Sept. 21"; MS Eng 327(73)
She [ ]tar, a muse whose holy spirit (incomplete) MS Eng 327 (25), 2
She that hath love and judgement too (incomplete) MS Eng 966.7, 41
She that intends ever in rest to be MS Eng 612, iii, 93v
She that through glass sees water run, doth see MS Eng 966.5, 170v; MS Eng 966.2, 28
She that to age her beauteous self resigns MS Thr 39, 11v
She that will eat her breakfast in her bed MS Eng 686, 20"; MS Eng 702, 3v
She to invite, the great God sent his star MS Eng 247.6, 2v
She took down her planet book (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 27
She was born at midnight in an Indian wild (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 41
She was both witty and zealous (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
She was seven year gaun and seven year comin' (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, in envelope fastened to back cover
She weeps, and yet looks fair as doth the face of day (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 15v
She went down to the Jew's garden MS Am 2349, xxv, 617
She wept alone for pleasures not to be (incomplete) MS Keats 2.17.2; MS Keats 2.17.3
She who has felt a real pain by Cupid's dart MS Eng 1038.1, 2v
She, who in others' words her silence breaks (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 135
She, whom all suppliants else implore MS Eng 785, 9v
She with her excellent wit and civil carriage MS Am 2349, xxi, 3
She whose high top above the stars did fare MS Eng 266, 59v
She wyled a wright to bare her chest (incomplete) MS Eng 1470, 254
Shed no tear! O shed no tear MS Keats 3.10 (4); MS Keats 2.22
Shelley styles his new poem "Prometheus Unbound" MS Eng 569.63, 25v
Sheltered in impotence, urge you to blows MS Eng 116.6, folder vi, 8
Shepherd divine, our wants relieve MS Eng 616, ii, 46v
Shepherd, wouldst thou here obtain MS Eng 611, i, 93
Shepherds! I have lost my love MS Eng 1038.1, 30v and 31
She's dead, and all which die MS Eng 966.3, 65; MS Eng 966.5, 146
She's taken him to her secret bower (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xviii, p. 27
She's virtuous and good, quoth he (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 38v
She's white as snow from head to foot (incomplete) MS Eng 612, ii, 56v
Shine forth, thou sun, bright ruler of the day (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 110v
Shoemaker, shoemaker, are you within MS Eng 1471, v, 37v
Shoots up, with dew drops streaming (incomplete) MS Mus 61, 1
Short is my rest whose toil is overlong MS Eng 1494, 21
Shou'd auld acquaintance be forgot MS Eng 1491 (4), i, 101v
Should a husband faithless rove MS Eng 569.65, 19v
Should auld acquaintance be forgot (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxi, 63
Shoul e'er the fair disdain you MS Eng 512, 10
Should I pretend to sing your praise MS Eng 584, 67v
Should I seek Hymen's tie MS Eng 1094, 63
Should my poor heart, O dearest Lord MS Eng 1503 (3), vol. ii, p. 203v
Should sorrow o'er thy brow MS Am 988, 11v
Should sovereign gold, the tyrant of mankind MS Eng 555, 20v
Sickness, be thou my soul's physician (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
Sieze, sieze the hour Ere it slips from you. Seldom comes the moment (incomplete) MS Keats 3.13, ii, 8v
Silence, brave gentlemen: If you will give an eye MS Eng 862, 36
Silence! coeval with eternity MS Keats 3.13, i, 15
Silence was first proclaimed in the divan (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 64v
Silent gentlemen Upon my custody MS Eng 1471, iii, 35
Silent, silent night MS Eng 1167, 57
Sillia with uncontested sway MS Eng 612, iii, 116v
Silly boy, there is no cause MS Eng 228, 27v
Silly's the heart of a woman (incomplete) MS Eng 616, i, 32
Silvia on her arm reclining MS Eng 895, 51
Silvia, wilt thou waste thy prime MS Eng 895, 81
Simon Brodie had a cow MS Am 1622 (29), 1
Sin, I would fain define thee, but thou art MS Eng 631, 43
Since all men that I come among MS Eng 626, 67
Since all the actions of the far famed men (incomplete) MS Eng 633, 58
Since all the riches of this world MS Eng 1167, 37; MS Eng 889, 31
Since Christ embraced the cross, dare I MS Eng 966.3, 111; MS Eng 966.7, 31; MS Eng 966.5, 10v; MS Eng 966.4, 92
Since churlish time hath lent thee life and health MS Eng 702, 27
Since, Cloris, you my passion know MS Eng 808 (8), 82
Since every foolish Coxcomb thinks it fit MS Eng 633, 12; MS Eng 585, 67v
Since fame is wight of wing, and through each climate flies MS Typ 14, 52
Since fancy of itself is loose and vain (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 134
Since fortune hath decreed that we should try MS Eng 702, 3
Since God hath blessed this northern climate cold MS Eng 623
Since I beheld you shaggy man MS Eng 569.68, 5
Since I must swing, I scorn, I scorn to wince or whine MS Eng 1038.1, 51v
Since in Norfolk your days you're determined to spend MS Eng 926, 52
Since laws were made for ev'ry degree MS Eng 1038.1, 52
Since love and verse, as well as wine MS Eng 633, 38; MS Eng 585, 191v
Since love hath in thine and mine eye MS Eng 895, 54v
Since man is frail, and all his thoughts are sin MS Typ 14, 6v
Since merit and reason give sanction to love MS Eng 834, folder 50
Since no more MS Eng 834, folder 51
Since now my Silvia is as kind as fair MS Eng 636F, 65v
Since now the world's turned upside down MS Eng 512, 25; MS Eng 629, 45
Since. O ye pow'rs, it is by your decree (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 99
Since, O ye powers, ye have bestow'd on me (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 73
Since our connubial bliss begun MS Eng 1323, 37
Since our good God with all surveying eye MS Eng 614, 4v
Since Palatine's come o'er MS Eng 895, 42v
Since, lovely sweet, much like unto a dewe MS Eng 626, 37v
Since of a rib first framed was a wife (incomplete) MS Eng 616, i, 28
Since public as highways and streets you are (incomplete) MS Eng 616, i, 5
Since satire is the only thing that's writ MS Eng 633, 17; MS Eng 585, 91
Since scandals fly thick MS Eng 633, 42; MS Eng 585, 207
Since she must go, and I must mourn, come night MS Eng 966.5, 73
Since some with barefac'd impudence deny MS Eng 640, 3
Since the sons of the muses grow numerous and loud MS Eng 623; MS Eng 636F, 75
Since the united cunning of the stage MS Eng 633, 30v; MS Eng 585, 154
Since the world's grown mad I'll e'en go sing MS Eng 633, 61v
Since times are so bad and are still growing worse MS Eng 1502 (1), folder 3, 1
Since 'tis now become a fashion MS Eng 808 (8), 59
Since, to restrain our joy, that ill-bred, rude MS Eng 623; MS Eng 636F, 40
Since truth breeds hate, thou must not take 't amiss MS Eng 645, 70
Since variety sweetens our lives MS Thr 198, folder 86
Since virtue can us not from death defend MS Eng 1278, folder 12-17, 17
Since we can die but once, and after death *EC7. Ox250.702p (originally ML 15.2F), item 7
Since we poor slavish women know MS Eng 808 (8), 27
Since wine, love, music present are MS Eng 540
Since you have forgot MS Eng 633, 42v; MS Eng 585, 210v
Since you, my dear, a country life admire MS Eng 611, i, 13
Since your bright and awful sex commands the town MS Eng 674, 7v
Since your curiosity led you so far MS Eng 629, 11v
Sing a sweet melodious measure MS Keats 3.13, ii, 24
Sing, heavenly muse MS Am 1919, 35v; MS Eng 768 (vol. 1), 23
Sing, Muse, the son of Maia and of Jove *EC8. Sh445. 929n, 28
Sing, O my spirit, sing MS Eng 611, iii, 43v
Sing we praises to the Lord, halleluia MS Eng 1038.1, 22
Sinks to the grave with unperceiv'd decay (incomplete) MS Eng 680, back cover
Sion Hill Delights me more, and Silva's Brook that flow'd (incomplete) MS Lowell 20 (43), 8
Sir, all this kind and courteous show MS Eng 247.5, 14
Sir, as for him that told me first 'twas true MS Eng 626, 40
Sir, as you always have until this hour MS Eng 247.5, 5v
Sir Carnegie tak hame your dochter (incomplete) MS Eng 1471, vii, 49
Sir Chaunticleer now ey'd the rising day (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 136
Sir, do you please, I pray, to have your ale (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 83
Sir, empty men Are trumpets of their own deserts; but you (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 34v
Sir, for your love you show but weak pretense (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 12v
Sir Gondibert leapt on his berry-brown steed MS Eng 692, 42v
Sir, I shall soon be in my teens MS Thr 198, folder 40
Sir, I thought good to send you a buckle MS Eng 1491 (4), ii, 269
Sir Joshua praised Rubens with a smile MS Eng 1167, 15; MS Eng 889, 8
Sir Joshua praises Michael Angelo MS Eng 1167, 15; MS Eng 889, 8
Sir Joshua sent his own portrait to MS Eng 1167, 17; MS Eng 889, 10
Sir, more than kisses, letters mingle souls MS Eng 966.3, 44v; MS Eng 966.1, 34v; MS Eng 966.7, 56v; MS Eng 966.5, 103v; MS Eng 966.4, 170
Sir, owe no spite to proverbs, or to them MS Eng 228, 27
Sir Ralph, a simple rural knight MS Eng 629, 72v
Sir Robert, who has merit and interest to show MS Eng 629, 46v
Sir Roger from a zealous piece of freeze MS Eng 631, 103
Sir Sherrif for thy sake (incomplete) MS Am 2349, xxv, 559
Sir, that same darksome cloud it is o'erpast MS Eng 626, 41
Sir, though (I thank God for it) I do hate MS Eng 966.3, 11; MS Eng 966.1, 7v; MS Eng 966.7, 68; MS Eng 966.5, 33; MS Eng 966.4, 126
Sir, when your noble verse I read MS Eng 584, 67
Sir, when your verse and lofty style I meet MS Eng 584, 67
Sir William Bishop made a knight MS Eng 569.65, 34v
Sirra', dost know the man that will drink free MS Eng 699, 27
Sister of Phoebus, gentle queen MS Eng 611, i, 106
Sit down in decent manner at your meat MS Eng 247.5, 48v
Sit you, merry gentlemen MS Eng 1507, Christmas carrols, 1767, 10; MS Eng 1507, Christmas carrols, [ca. 1777], 7
Sithe age, alas, with hoary hairs to deck me hath begun MS Eng 757, 111
Sithence all endeavors to advancement move MS Eng 645, 17v
Sithence faithless man is grown MS Eng 645, 26
Sithence that the rebels now are there MS Eng 645, 24v
Sits couerst unknown Autograph file, D: John Digmore, 2
Sitting and ready to be drawn MS Eng 703, 59"; MS Eng 626, 68v
Sitting in that old state arabian (incomplete) MS Keats 3.2, 239
Sitting late with sorrow sleeping MS Eng 1495, 12
Six and six nobles gaed to Bethelvie fair MS Eng 1471, v, 220
Six tedious months young Damon sighed MS Eng 692, 57
Skales tower three times three ascend, arch traitor thou MS Eng 645, 91v
Slaep'ry Sim o' the Lamb Hill MS Eng 862, 152
Slaughter and knocking on the head (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 62
Slave, let me die a queen, in all my pride (incomplete) MS Eng 611, iii, 25v
Sleep, close not up mine eyes, and if thou do MS Eng 626, 19
Sleep, next society and true friendship MS Eng 966.3, 9; MS Eng 966.7, 78v; MS Eng 966.5, 45v; MS Eng 966.4, 119v
Sleep, O Sleep, with the rod of incantation charm my imagination MS Eng 1038.1, 5
Sleep, Ormando, void of fear MS Eng 512, 8
Sleep, sleep, beauty bright MS Eng 1167, 68
Sleep, sleep: in thy sleep MS Eng 1167, 58; MS Eng 889, 48
Sleep, sleep, old sun, thou canst not have repast MS Eng 966.3, 112; MS Eng 966.5, 12v
Sleeping Sim in the lamb hill MS Eng 862, 145
Sleeping Sim o' the Lam-hill MS Eng 1500, 40v
Sleep'st thou, or wak'st thou, Lord Montgomerie MS Eng 1471, i, 170
Slow comes the hour; its passing speed how great MS Keats 3.13, i, 7v
Slow rose the mists of nightthe moonbeams gleamed MS Eng 265.3, 128v
Slow sinks, more lovely ere his race be run MS Eng 1485, 2
Slow to be warmed, yet quick to rove MS Eng 569.68, 3
Slow to the court the pensive king returns (incomplete) MS Eng 611, i, 85v
Slumb'ring in cold moonbeams MS Mus 237, i, 8
Small busy flames play thro' the fresh laid coals MS Keats 3.12, 46v; MS Keats 3.5, p. 16; MS Keats 2.5, 1; MS Keats 2.6, 1
Small flames are pricking through the fresh laid coals MS Keats 2.2, 1
Small is the praise of beauty when it flies (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 116
Small service is true service while it lasts MS Eng 327(36)
Smectymnis? The goblin makes me start MS Eng 703, 79
Smile, and wave a chair with comely grace, too (incomplete) MS Eng 265.6, v. 2
Smile, fair ones, and your slave frim slender tree MS Thr 21, 4
Smile, smile MS Eng 834, folder 53
Smug, the smith, for ale and spice MS Eng 966.7, 24v
Snatched from our longing, hoping eyes MS Eng 703, 41
Snow falling, Julia me did press MS Eng 645, 23
So a consummate knave in others' eyes (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 133
So a wild Tartar when he spies (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 62
So all in fire Elijah fled unkind MS Eng 612, iii, 71
So angels love; so let them love for me MS Eng 631, 75
So as I lay this othir nyght MS Eng 1482, Harl 2255, 128v
So, at last, This nail is in my temples (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 124
So bakers think it no collusion (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 79v
So be or else but seldom busied best MS Eng 1285, 73
So boys unlucky near a river's side (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 133
So choice a piece of beauty and of wit MS Eng 703, 14v
So closely, closely pressed MS Eng 808 (8), 72
So did I humbly reverence each degree MS Eng 966.5, 123
So do, Lucilius, thee to thee restore MS Eng 623
So does the little gnat, by night (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 103v
So does the sun withdraw his beams MS Eng 808 (8), 57
So doubtful hills the wearied pilgrim sees (incomplete) MS Eng 731, folder 275, 10
So early bloomed and so untimely died MS Eng 629, 25
So envious witches, on the least disgust (incomplete) MS Eng 611, ii, 68v
So fancy, to the musing poet's eye (incomplete) *EC8. W8915.838s, "Dedication" leaf
So far, I doubt not, but you'll find it clear (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 84v
So firmly fond (incomplete) MS Mus 61, 1
So flies like us the timid hare MS Thr 198, folder 90
So flow'rs, when blasting winds invade (incomplete) MS Eng 612, iii, 105v
So from that cry over the boundless hills (incomplete) MS Eng 1274, ch. 109